Director Hideaki Anno, who has always been receiving a lot of attention from fans along with Neon Genesis Evangelion
In the 26th episode "Magokoro wo Kimi ni" released at the theater, he caught the hearts of many fans with his outstanding performance.
What does he have in his mind when making a film?
It's that the viewers do not fall asleep.
How can I avoid the viewers to sleep while watching?
I'm thinking about nothing but that.
If you want to use CG efficiently, anime-like movies are the best.
CG is similar to animation, so if you use it in live action it will look more like animation.
There is not much need to use CG for animation.
[What is the role of CG in animation production?]
I was able to make animation without CG. I think I'm using it now just because it's novel.
People who are making anime aren't interested in CG so much.
He released unique images in live-action works as well such as Cutie Honey, which was released recently and became a hot topic, Love & Pop and Shiki-Jitsu.
He is demonstrating his talent by jumping over the genre of anime.
I haven't done tokusatsu in a commercial movie yet, so I want to do a tokusatsu movie.
[What is the difference between anime and live-action production?]
The staff members are in a completely different field.
Also, between animation and live-action, the flow of time is completely different, so that's a big thing.